<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>heavy metals on Geoscience Blog</title>
    <link>https://webaoz2.netlify.app/tags/heavy-metals/</link>
    <description>Recent content in heavy metals on Geoscience Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://webaoz2.netlify.app/tags/heavy-metals/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Evaluación hidrogeológica y geoambiental en la comunidad de contacto inicial Santa Rosa de Serjali. Región Ucayali, provincia Atalaya, distrito Sepahua</title>
      <link>https://webaoz2.netlify.app/research/hydrogeology-geoenvironmental/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://webaoz2.netlify.app/research/hydrogeology-geoenvironmental/</guid>
      <description>Hydrogeological Evaluation and Geoenvironmental in the initial contact community Santa Rosa of Serjali. Ucayali Region, Atalaya province, district Sepahua - Peru.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Estudio de línea base geoambiental de las subcuencas Vilcabamba, Santo Tomás y Alto Apurímac (Cusco - Apurímac) - [Boletín N 1]</title>
      <link>https://webaoz2.netlify.app/research/lbg-cusco-apurimac/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://webaoz2.netlify.app/research/lbg-cusco-apurimac/</guid>
      <description>Geoenvironmental Base Line Research in the subbasins Vilcabamba, Santo Tomas and Alto Apurimac (Cusco-Apurímac), Peru.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Study to Determine Levels of Cadmium in Cocoa Crops Applied to Inland Areas of Peru: “The Case of the Campo Verde-Honoria Tournavista Corridor”</title>
      <link>https://webaoz2.netlify.app/research/geostatistics-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://webaoz2.netlify.app/research/geostatistics-r/</guid>
      <description>An study to determine levels of Cd in Cocoa Crops in Ucayali.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inspección técnica de línea base geoambiental de la cuenca del río Puyango-Tumbes (lado peruano). Región Tumbes</title>
      <link>https://webaoz2.netlify.app/research/lbg-tumbes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://webaoz2.netlify.app/research/lbg-tumbes/</guid>
      <description>Geoenvironmental Base Line Inspection of River Puyango-Tumbes (peruvian side) that allows determinated that source of heavy metals come from Puyango in Ecuador.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
