<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Geoscience Blog</title>
    <link>https://webaoz2.netlify.app/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Geoscience Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://webaoz2.netlify.app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning in Geological Hazards</title>
      <link>https://webaoz2.netlify.app/blog/spoonful-series/01-spoonful/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://webaoz2.netlify.app/blog/spoonful-series/01-spoonful/</guid>
      <description>Is coming soon      Let&amp;rsquo;s start (soon).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exploratory Analysis and Concepts in Water Resource</title>
      <link>https://webaoz2.netlify.app/blog/spoonful-series/02-spoonful/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://webaoz2.netlify.app/blog/spoonful-series/02-spoonful/</guid>
      <description> Coming soon      Coming soon     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automated Reports with Parameters</title>
      <link>https://webaoz2.netlify.app/blog/spoonful-series/03-spoonful/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://webaoz2.netlify.app/blog/spoonful-series/03-spoonful/</guid>
      <description>¿What is an automated report with parameters?     Well, in simple terms an automated report is a document in any format (.docx, .ppt, .pdf, .html and so on) that can be update in a specific time window iteratively while is required, in the case refer to parameters, there are some variables that can be change, for example, basin, sub-basin, department, province, geological horizont, lake, etc. (espacial) and hourly, daily, monthly , etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Surface Water Analysis - Non Spatial I</title>
      <link>https://webaoz2.netlify.app/blog/2021-12-27-surface-water-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://webaoz2.netlify.app/blog/2021-12-27-surface-water-analysis/</guid>
      <description>Subbasin Alto Camaná - Arequipa</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evaluación hidrogeológica y geoambiental en la comunidad de contacto inicial Santa Rosa de Serjali. Región Ucayali, provincia Atalaya, distrito Sepahua</title>
      <link>https://webaoz2.netlify.app/research/hydrogeology-geoenvironmental/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://webaoz2.netlify.app/research/hydrogeology-geoenvironmental/</guid>
      <description>Hydrogeological Evaluation and Geoenvironmental in the initial contact community Santa Rosa of Serjali. Ucayali Region, Atalaya province, district Sepahua - Peru.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Estudio de línea base geoambiental de las subcuencas Vilcabamba, Santo Tomás y Alto Apurímac (Cusco - Apurímac) - [Boletín N 1]</title>
      <link>https://webaoz2.netlify.app/research/lbg-cusco-apurimac/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://webaoz2.netlify.app/research/lbg-cusco-apurimac/</guid>
      <description>Geoenvironmental Base Line Research in the subbasins Vilcabamba, Santo Tomas and Alto Apurimac (Cusco-Apurímac), Peru.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Geoscience Multiverse</title>
      <link>https://webaoz2.netlify.app/talk/second-seedling/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 14:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://webaoz2.netlify.app/talk/second-seedling/</guid>
      <description>Panorama     El curso desarrolla desde los conceptos básicos de geodatabase (base de datos geoespacial) para entender la estructura y funcionamiento de base de datos espacial. Además se realiza el análisis estadístico exploratorio de aguas, suelo, rocas y sedimentos de drenaje, así como modelos estadísticos, geoestadísticos y de machine learning para su aplicación en recursos hídricos, geoquímica, hidroquímica, peligros geológicos, rock blasting todo esto enmarcado en la interactividad y desarrollo web.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Study to Determine Levels of Cadmium in Cocoa Crops Applied to Inland Areas of Peru: “The Case of the Campo Verde-Honoria Tournavista Corridor”</title>
      <link>https://webaoz2.netlify.app/research/geostatistics-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://webaoz2.netlify.app/research/geostatistics-r/</guid>
      <description>An study to determine levels of Cd in Cocoa Crops in Ucayali.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Statical Data Analysis Applied to Geology</title>
      <link>https://webaoz2.netlify.app/talk/campfire/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://webaoz2.netlify.app/talk/campfire/</guid>
      <description>I was really excited to give this talk! Stay tuned for video and slides.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inspección técnica de línea base geoambiental de la cuenca del río Puyango-Tumbes (lado peruano). Región Tumbes</title>
      <link>https://webaoz2.netlify.app/research/lbg-tumbes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://webaoz2.netlify.app/research/lbg-tumbes/</guid>
      <description>Geoenvironmental Base Line Inspection of River Puyango-Tumbes (peruvian side) that allows determinated that source of heavy metals come from Puyango in Ecuador.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Next Project</title>
      <link>https://webaoz2.netlify.app/project/penguins/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://webaoz2.netlify.app/project/penguins/</guid>
      <description> “Something is going to come soon. So stay fullish, stay hungry.”     — Alonso Otiniano, Ist working on this application [^1]
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://webaoz2.netlify.app/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2019 13:38:41 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://webaoz2.netlify.app/contact/</guid>
      <description>** Contact page don&amp;rsquo;t contain a body, just the front matter above. See form.html in the layouts folder.
Formspree requires a (free) account and new form to be set up. The link is made on the final published url in the field: Restrict to Domain. It is possible to register up to 2 emails free and you can select which one you want the forms to go to within Formspree in the Settings tab.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contributors</title>
      <link>https://webaoz2.netlify.app/contributors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://webaoz2.netlify.app/contributors/</guid>
      <description>Thank you everyone who has contributed both technical and creative skills to this project:
   Ing. Joseps Andrade Choque: for the support and guidance in working with html and web applications.
   Dr. Carlos Benavente: for the opportunity to apply artificial intelligence to geology and the freedom to explore this new geoscience multiverse.
   Dr. Jimmy Rosales: for trusting in my work and experience in geological geostatistics and machine learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hydroapp Web Data Analysis</title>
      <link>https://webaoz2.netlify.app/project/giraffes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://webaoz2.netlify.app/project/giraffes/</guid>
      <description>Hidroapp is a design system that allows you to analyze data online related to hydrochemical resources.      Data     The data sample is on the following link data link.
The data contains the following columns:
  Quantitative Variables:
 pH Ce TDS Ca K Mg Na Cl SO4 HCO3 CO3    Qualitative Variables:
 Codigo (Identifier) Temporada (Seasonality) Tipo_Fuente (Water Classification) Clase_Fuente (Surface and Subterranean Classification) ratingcol claseph    The quantitative variables are physico-chemical parameters, meanwhile the qualitative variables are the Codigo (Identifier), Temporada(Dry-&amp;ldquo;Estiaje&amp;rdquo; or Wet-&amp;ldquo;Avenida&amp;rdquo; season), Tipo_Fuente(Surface-&amp;ldquo;Superficial&amp;rdquo; or Subsurface-&amp;ldquo;Subterranean&amp;rdquo;), Clase_Fuente(), ratingcol-claseph (3 colors to mention if blue-basic, green-neutral or red-acid).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>License</title>
      <link>https://webaoz2.netlify.app/license/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://webaoz2.netlify.app/license/</guid>
      <description>My blog posts are released under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
